School BUS App
Driver App
Parents App
Arun- can look at this appàfor comparisonà. 
Comments on our App
On this page- suggested to capture- Parent Contact, Grade, Level, DOB, Age- sample below
Suppose to have search function here right?
This one û can it be any way that from the backend we can control the time that they can choose. Fixed time of 3:00 and 4:00, etc?
Parent contact number û if can column for two numbers
This looks nicer then what we have. We should have to upload photo but not compulsory for now.
This one- driver have to checkout to populate-ok
This same like as our self-pickup but it appears as alternative in the list so driver knows parent is self picking up?
